Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Do you even like Hyo Seon's dad?
Why are you asking me something like that?
Tell me you at least like him a little!
If you say he's not just someone you can take a lot from,
but someone you actually like,
then I'll forgive you.
Why are you causing such a fuss?
I like him, why?
I like him. I like him because he has a lot I can take from him! Why?
Don't smile at people you can't get anything from.
Don't trust anyone who just smiles your way, either.
Do you know what it means to live?
No matter how hard to study and show off that brain of yours,
you will never know how hard it is to get by.
Episode 7
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
I'm just upset it's been confirmed with what she said.
It's not like I didn't know before.
What?
Did you think I wouldn't know
how your mother felt about me?
I need to go back to the factory. Take a taxi back home with Mom.
Don't tell your mom that I heard you two talking.
If she knows, then she'll try hard to redeem herself.
I don't want to see her trying too hard.
When Eun Jo first became family,
I was really happy I had an older sister
and I really liked Eun Jo,
even though she kept pushing me away.
Whenever Eun Jo made conversation with me,
I liked it so much I laughed all day.
Even if she cursed at me, I was happy.
How could she
How can she do this to me?
How can she make my worrying about her seem so pitiful?
Don't cry.
Cut it out.
Stolen? Who's stealing from you?
If you don't want to get it stolen, then pay attention and protect what's yours!
Why...
are you yelling at me?
Why? Can I not yell at you?
Is no one allowed to be angry at you?
Do we have to be proud of everything you do?
- Oppa...
- We accept it, laugh, and clap for you. Is that all we should do?
Why are you so immature?
What have you made yourself, with your own efforts, without leaning on anyone else?
What have you done with your own hands and own strength?
Did Eun Jo take it from you?
How could she take it from you when you've never earned anything?
What is it? Why are you looking?
Why are you looking at me like that? Do you feel wronged?
Are you angry I'm not taking your side?
I'm not yours, you punk!
I dare you to cry. If you do, I won't let you be.
Oppa ... Don't do that. I'm afraid.
I said stop it!
Oppa, why are you being like this?
Stop
Your enemy is not Eun Jo. You should make your own things.
And the things you make, you should protect.
If you don't do that, even if things get taken from you, you can't say anything about it. Understand?
You'll have nothing to say even if it's taken from you!
Don't rely on me either. Even if you rely on me, I won't accept it.
In the time you spend whining like this, you should clean one more jar.
Hurry up and grow into an adult.
Hurry.
Get in.
Aren't you getting in?
Wow, you're good at this!
Yes, I'm good.
Should we scout him to the kitchen?
That'll be hard to do. I'm quite expensive, so you'll need to double the wage.
Goodness. You should head out now. I heard you're going on a picnic today?
I'll follow them after I'm done with this. I'll do it.
Hello?
Is this the place you make Daeseong rice wine or Daeseong fake rice wine?
- What?
- You're all dead! Where are you?
How dare you joke around with food? Let me speak to your CEO!
Hello? Who are you? What do you mean, joke around?
Stop saying hello this and hello that.
Stay right there! I'm heading over!
Are you here alone?
Who are you?
The kitchen granny's told me to give this to your eldest daughter.
She didn't come with me.
I told you to go in and rest.
You need to rest. Head home.
How... can you do that?
Even though you know... how?
Know what?
After knowing that she's by my side only
because she has things to take from me?
Yes.
That's alright.
Why? Why is that alright?
How can that be okay? Until when was it okay?
If you knew, how could you let Mom... and me?
I take pity on your mother,
who can't help but think the way she does.
When you first came to me,
and spoke whatever came to your mind,
as you had learned from your mother,
I thought how nice it would be if I could go into your past,
before you met me, and protect you.
I took pity on you enough to think those thoughts.
It doesn't matter, because I love your mother.
Getting my things taken from me
is much better than you or your mother not being by my side.
I'm telling you the truth.
Goodness... This won't do.
You can't cry like this, you're supposed to be resting.
Come on, let's go home. Let's rest today.
Do you want to go follow the others out on their picnic?
We can go see the flowers. Shall we take Gi Hoon?
What can I do?
Don't abandon me.
If you do that, then I'll be grateful.
Let's go!
♫  In the depth of my heart ♫
♫ When loneliness comes again ♫
♫  I also don't know again what you intend ♫
♫  Without saying anything, smile again ♫
♫  More than saying you loved me ♫
♫  while you silently look at me ♫
♫  I said I liked you so much and loved you ♫
♫  My love, will you run to me? ♫
Head it!
♫  I too unconsciously am waiting for you. ♫
♫  I too unconsciously am waiting for you ♫
Give it to me.
♫ I am going to love you this way ♫
Unknown Caller
- Hello?
- Where are you? I'm at the office alone, without trying to rely on anyone.
I'm trying to do something, but I don't know how to.
Try it. I said try it! Is this rice wine or poop?
Don't you know what happens when you mess around with food?
Tell your president to come out! Isn't he here?
Why?
What's wrong with the taste?
What would we say with you, miss? Go call the president!
Does it taste weird? How is it weird?
Give me that.
- It's spoiled.
- How could you sell spoiled alcohol?
This is spoiled, too!
Tell the president to come out!
You should have a conscience when trying to do business. Is he in here?
But misters!
This isn't our rice wine.
The bottles are our bottles, but the alcohol inside isn't ours.
Goodness... What do you mean that isn't alcohol from here?
These days, we don't have any leftover stock because our rice wine sells well,
but when we used to have leftover stock, we used to make vinegar with it.
It wouldn't become so spoiled to the point of undrinkable,
just because its expiration date passes.
This definitely isn't our alcohol. I know it well.
Do you want to make a bet with me?
If you lose the bet, what do you want to give up?
Has something like this happened before?
No. Hurry up. Hyo Seon is alone.
I know. I'm going quickly.
Cheers!
Drink up. Drink, drink!
Have another glass. Isn't it delicious?
Ever since I was born, I ws given my mother's milk half the time,
and Daeseong's rice wine the other half the time.
That's how I grew up.
There's no way I wouldn't know the taste of our alcohol.
The vinegar you make with our rice wine tastes...
Um... Gosh.
I can't explain it with words. Why aren't they coming?
I asked granny to bring us some vinegar.
What about we take another shot and sing a few more songs while we wait?
Sounds good! Have another shot!
Here, here!
One, two, three, four-
Dad,
This isn't our alcohol. It's not our alcohol, but it's in our bottles.
The rice wine tastes great!
Drink up!
Hello. I'm Goo Dae Seong, president of Dae Seong True Winemakers.
Oh, you're the president!
It's spoiled.
I told you it was spoiled. You don't believe me, do you?
You had to check it for yourself because you couldn't believe me?
Who mixed a different rice wine with ours? Where did they get this?
Jumbo Supermarket (a supermarket is actually a small corner convenience store with produce) in Bangbae-dong.
Bangbae-dong?
What I'm saying is...
You need to understand what I'm saying.
No matter who asks, say you don't know.
How much money did you get from me?
Since you got that, you need to stay quiet.
Goodness, this little punk has organs the size of the pea!
What do you mean, my organs are the size of a pea? Have you forgotten where I'm from?
Shut up, you punk.
Daeseong Company, which illegally distributed barrels of makgeolli (rice wine), was finally caught.
Detection of high levels of Sodium Saccharin discovered.
As a result of the inspection to Daeseong Conpany which illegally distributed barrels of makgeolli,
Sodium Saccharin, an additive prohibited in making makgeolli, was detected by Korea Food and Drug Administration.
The expiration date of our wine is
shorter compared to other brands of wine.
Other brands of rice wine use additional preservatives
or high-temperature sterilization to extend the shelf-life of their wine.
But, we don't use that method.
A day before the labelled expiration date,
we collect any unsold remaining product.
Because we have recently not had anything left unsold, there was no reason to collect expired product.
Are you advertising your wine right in front of the police right now?
Do you want us to buy more?
There is no evidence anywhere in our production process to show
that we added prohibited additive Sodium Saccharin in our makgeolli (rice wine).
You already investigated.
However, thereis Sodium Saccharin found in the spoilt wine in question.
That is something someone malicious has done to slander our alcohol.
This is definitely not a problem with the manufacturing process,
but a problem with the distribution process for sure.
Please investigate the distribution process.
We will try our best to cooperate in the investigation without hiding anything
We never said we wouldn't cooperate.
Isn't it your duty to finish the investigation as soon as possible?
We have been repeating ourselves for a few days already.
In the meantime, it's just not only the spoilt wine in question that is being distributed in our region...
Returns are coming in from other parts of the country and we have lost all of our orders.
Don't get agitated.
It will be fine.
What should we do?
Oh, right.
You've told me not to rely on anyone right?
Is there nothing that I can do at this time?
Can I not even ask this?
Is asking a question relying on you as well?
I understand.
I won't ask anymore.
It's a relief that this happened before we expanded our facilities.
If we had expanded, we would have produced more and more would be returned.
It can be solved,
So don't worry about it.
Can you say it to me one more time, Oppa?
Just now, it's just like when you said the moon is square, right?
You said it can be solved
and asked me not to worry.
I really felt like it can be solved...
So I don't have to worry.
If you entrusted it to me then you should have waited. It's not even a child's play.
What kind of recklessness is this?
Do you think you can get Dae Seong True Winemakers through this method?
It's not me.
It's not?
Do I look like someone who would play games like this?
Then is it Gi Jeong?
You really don't know me or Gi Jeong at all, do you?
It's not me or Gi Jeong.
The blow to their reputation will be huge.
Both Gi Jeong and I are likely thinking the same thing.
We are thankful for help to someone we don't know.
Don't even try to pull something at this opportunity. Wait.
Just what are you intending to do?
I'm going to take over Daeseong before Gi Jeong can,
and bloody his nose in the process.
I'm not going to make Daeseong fail due to its ruined reputation.
I'm going to take it. I don't want something that's failed.
I'm going to develop it and take it. That's best for you, too.
Is that so? Father and Gi Hoon?
Yes.
Gi Hoon, by any chance didn't he enter Dae Seong True Winemakers already?
What is father planning?
Since Gi Hoon has returned,
but hasn't stayed properly motivated,
I think he told him to just remain there.
Father's minion.
You don't like the term "minion", do you?
Well, I guess, I must use it.
As father's minion, you assisted him for a long time.
Can't you let your feelings go?
You think my father does not know that you and I are talking?
He knows what Gi Hoon is planning, but is pretending not to know.
That's the kind of person he is.
Father can read your intentions like a book.
Why can't you read his?
Try reading it.
I understand.
You can leave now.
Yes, sir.
Are they failing?
- What?
- Is this business going to fail?
What's going to happen? Can we get anything from it?
If the factory fails, can we not even get the company?
What about this house? Can we take the house?
You have to focus.
Before everything goes to shambles,
secretly prepare at least a house.
Make everything you can make yours on paper.
Stop.
Mom, please. Please stop.
What do you mean, please stop?
They're not going to fail. Even if they do,
they'll be lots for you to take.
Very very much.
You'll die from being so stuffed you can't breathe,
but not because you starved.
Really?
Okay then.
How many envelopes of money did I give you?
Since you accepted that, you have to stay quiet, too.
♫ In the colors... (In Spanish}
♫ In the colors is the rainbow that we see shining? (In Spanish}
♫ And that is why I love the great loves of many colors(In Spanish}
♫ In the solicitude which wakes me up ♫
♫when I wake up from an exhausted sleep♫
♫because I still remember you smiling♫
♫I'm secretly smiling♫
♫Love leaves again this way♫
Excuse me.
♫When the beautiful season arrives ♫
- Excuse me.
- What?
Excuse me, the thing is that...
It's nothing. Salute.
♫I am living day after day ♫
♫In your name when tears appear, ah♫
♫I can't bear it so I can't laugh♫
♫I'll call out your name again♫
Turn off the light.
Let's give this a try. Between us.
What are you talking about?
I won't let you have everything.
There was a time when I wanted to be like you.
You did well in your studies, you were smart, and haughty.
And also... your I-don't-need-anyone attitude.
Even if no one is looking, that look of arrogance as if it's nothing.
There was a time when I thought you were so cool.
But then you always splashed cold water on whatever I longed for.
Let's give this a try. I'm not sure what I'm supposed to do yet,
but I said let's give it a try.
- Open it.
- Yes.
I had no idea this was what he was doing.
He said just to have a taste, so I did only taste it.
Looks like they mixed the drinks here. President, over there.
Dae Seong True Wine Makers makgeolli
♫ Whatever it is you wanted, I did everything for you
Fun Fun - Joo Joo Club
♫ Today for me
I'm telling you this...
I had bought land that was abandoned you know? It'll soon be developed.
If we just do the presentation then this will double!
Girls! Girls! Just trust me! I will buy you a diamond ring that's as big as an egg.
I'm... against it.
He's my mom's little brother.
We can't call the police to catch my uncle who has ran away.
The production in the factory has completely stopped.
If we are to get rid of this wronged incident and run the factories,
He's my uncle! He has nowhere else to go.
Where and what on earth is he doing?
We don't have time. You'd better make a decision on this.
I... while also protecting Hyo Seon's uncle
we need to think of a way to save the factory.
How much time...
How much time is needed to recover the broken trust
and if it will even be recovered, that we don't know.
Slowly... we can go slow.
I can't do that. Are we in a circumstance where we can do that?
We want to have a TV ad but even if our budget was at it's best--
That's enough. Let's take it easy.
We can start again slowly.
Let's think of a way to redeem ourselves after we've posted an apology notice in the newspapers.
Are you crazy? Why would we release an apology when we've done nothing wrong?
It is the fault of the corporation for not being able to control its employees.
I can't believe he did it alone.
I'm sure there are others involved.
If no one else will, I will report it to the police.
Try to understand the president's wishes.
Stop acting like you're better than everyone.
Daeseong Company can recover quickly.
Because the taste of our wine is better than that of others,
people are already thinking that it's a good thing Dae Seong's rice wine won't be getting too much attention,
and we're getting calls that we've never gotten before.
Are you talking about the single call we got last week?
Do you think that was really an interest call?
Shouldn't you be producing more? Aren't you going to run your factories? Can we run them for you?
There are already thieves lining up to swallow Daeseung Company whole, you naive idiot.
At my insistence we spent lavish amounts of money on a commercial,
but now I want to die because of everything that got canceled thanks to this incident. Do you know that?
Wait. Talk to me for a bit. What does that mean? Are others going to take over?
Move.
Tell me a bit more in detail!
Let go of her, then speak.
Where is that? Can't you find out?
Why does it matter to you? We're not going to sell it.
Move!
No, no. We won't meet you. If you want to meet about that, then there's no reason for us to meet.
No, no. Please don't come.
Daeseung Company will not fail because of something like this.
We will not sell it to anyone!
Gosh...
Dad...
Dad?
You haven't shaved, have you?
Why are you being like this?
I want to be someone whom you find helpful
and you can rely on.
I really want to do that,
but I'm nothing, right?
Why would you say that?
Right now, I may be nothing,
but I'll slowly become your strength, Dad.
Really?
Your face is so pale. What is this?
- Forget it.
- Here, too. Here.
Right here, too.
Go in. Aren't you going to go in? Let's go in together.
If we're able to succeed in the Japanese markets, word will get out that sales were successful overseas
and the chances of domestic markets reopening become high.
It'll be good for us even if we can't get into the markets deeply.
Daeseung Company will make the winning move with the taste of our rice wine.
The japanese customers who had tasted the Daeseong Company. cloud liquor distributed in the hotels,
were very favorable, which is a very good omen for hope.
Okay. We have to at least to something.
What do you think, Eun Jo?
I'll go on a business trip to Japan.
I'd like to analyze the local situation myself.
I'll go.
Really?
I'll go with Hyo Seon.
To my knowledge, Hyo Seon wants to turn a new leaf
and I think this business trip will help her.
You said you wouldn't let me rely on you.
Or anyone...
I'm not letting you rely on anyone.
I'm going to show you what you have to do if you don't want to get anything taken from you.
You said Eun Jo didn't take anything from me.
When not only Eun Jo, but anyone, tries to take something from you and attacks,
you need to protect it.
These are the plane tickets and vouchers for the hotel.
I've also included a list of people to meet and their contacts.
He said to sleep early, because you need to leave early in the morning tomorrow.
Excuse me. The president wants to see you.
Excuse me, Mr. Han Jeong Woo.
Why have you packed your things?
Aren't I getting chased out?
I've figured out where Hyo Seon's uncle went.
You'll go with me together, tomorrow.
To...gether?
Leave your belongings and follow me.
You found out where Uncle is?
What?
It's nothing.
Stop looking around and focus on driving.
Yes, I understand.
When I was younger, as someone cut kimchi,
if I ate kimchi like this next to them,
the person cutting the kimchi would slap my hand away.
I'm just saying.
Why aren't you finishing your food?
You and I never had leftovers.
Sit down and finish it all, Noona.
I told you,
wherever you're living and whatever you're doing, I'd find you, and your life...
You're that Han Jeong Woo?
I wondered when you would recognize me. It took you so long.
You're that Jeong Woo?
That's what I said.
You still can't believe it? I am that Jeong Woo.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I told you I was waiting until you would recognize me.
I just told you since you really weren't catching on.
If I hadn't told you, then you would've never recognized me, would you?
How could I recognize that this Jeong Woo is the same as that Jeong Woo?
Is your heart fluttering because of how handsome I've become?
If you mess around, I'll hit you.
Hit me. I really want to get hit with those hands of yours.
We were told he had stayed here for sure.
He was here. Did I say he wasn't?
He was here for multiple days, but ran away without even paying his balance!
Did he not tell you where he was going?
Hey. Have you seen someone running away tell you where he'd be going before he left?
How are you related to him? You should pay for his stay instead of him!
He left?
I don't think he'll return.
I heard he bought land with the money he earned from selling the spoiled alcohol,
but it seemed he was scammed in that.
I think he ran away because he was so ashamed.
I'm waiting for someone to contact me,
so don't go anywhere far and just wait a bit there.
Honey, Joon Soo is excited about going on a trip with you. He's waiting.
Okay, sure.
Are you feeling sick somewhere?
No... I'm okay.
You haven't even been able to rest these days because you've got so much on your plate.
You should rest a bit for now. Play with Joon Soo next time.
Spending time with my son is resting.
Will you really be okay?
I told you I'm fine.
Daddy!
My little Joon Soo.
Okay, let's go!
Japan
Oppa,
do you know how to speak Japanese?
I don't know how to speak a single word.
It's okay. They're distinguished representatives from the liquor marketing in Japan.
They studied Korean because they're fans of Korean dramas.
Hello.
- It's delicious.
- Super good.
Even Hallyu actors drink this alcohol.
In Korea, we can guarantee that there is no other that compares to the taste of our rice wines.
Though we can't compare to the size of larger corporations,
the taste of our alcohols is shaking up the Korean markets.
I know this person.
We saw her commercial on YouTube.
You're very beautiful.
Thank you.
My son is usually very quiet, but he saw your video
and talks to be about you a lot,
saying you're very pretty.
I see.
I know this isn't very courteous, but I'd like to invite you to my house
before you leave.
I think my son would be impressed.
We will gratefully accept your invitation.
Thank you.
- What is it?
- Take it. It's yours.
I saved up everything,
without taking a single cent, from what I earned in the Marines.
It's not a lot, but it's my entire life's savings.
Why are you giving this to me?
I saved it up to give it to you.
Exactly. Why did you save it up for me?
This woman.. Are you asking because you really don't know?
Who else would I give my first earnings to?
How is Mr. Jang doing?
Never mind, forget it. Don't answer. I'm not curious.
I don't know either.
I... lived alone ever since I was 16.
To be exact, I wasn't alone.
I lived with you.
What about baseball? Did you quit baseball?
Stop messing around.
Okay.
I'll take this for now.
Really?
I'll give it to you when you get married, along with interest or some more funds.
Hello?
Oppa.
Oppa!
What is it?
Oppa...
Dad...
What about the president?
Dad... fainted.
Dad fainted after he went to go play with Joon Soo.
♫ Like this for another day, month or year
♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt. ♫
Are you treating me like a crazy woman right now, Granny?
With Father...
- Are you okay?
- My heart is beating quickly.
If you treat Hyo Seon poorly, I'll kill you with my own hands.
You can just pretend I'm not here.
Let go! Let go!
Until where are you going to run? I'll run for you.
♫ Can't you hear my voice? ♫